class ReadingData {
  static List<QuestionAnswer> readingFillInBlankList = [
    QuestionAnswer(
        question:
            'In paragraph one, the writer suggests that companies could consider',
        answer: """abolishing pay schemes that are based on age
"""),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: 'Skill Team is an example of a company which',
        answer: """Allows the expertise of older workers to be put to use.

"""),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: 'According to the writer, ‘bridge’ jobs ',
        answer: """Appeal to distinct groups of older worker

"""),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: 'David Store’s study found that',
        answer: """older people are good at running their own businesses

"""),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: 'The sixteenth century was an age of great ___exploration.',
        answer: """Land

"""),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question:
            'Magellan lost the favor of the king of Portugal when he became involved in a political ___.',
        answer: """Entanglement

"""),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question:
            'The Pope divided New World lands between Spain and Portugal according to their location on one side or the other of an imaginary geographical line 50 degrees west of Greenwich that extends in a ___ direction.',
        answer: """north and south

"""),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question:
            'One of Magellans ships explored the ___ of South America for a passage across the continent.',
        answer: """physical features

"""),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question:
            'Four of the ships sought a passage along a southern _________.',
        answer: """  body of land with water on three sides 

"""),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: 'The passage was found near 50 degrees S of ___________',
        answer: """The equator 

"""),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question:
            'In the spring of 1521, the ships crossed the ___ now called the International Date Line.',
        answer: """imaginary circle passing through the poles

"""),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question:
            'The Curies __________ collaboration helped to unlock the secrets of the atom.',
        answer: """Friendly
"""),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: '. Marie had a bright mind and a _________ personality.',
        answer: """lighthearted
"""),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question:
            'When she learned that she could not attend the university in Warsaw, she felt _______________.',
        answer: """annoyed
"""),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question:
            'Marie ___ by leaving Poland and traveling to France to enter the Sorbonne.',
        answer: """challenged authority 

"""),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: '_____she remembered their joy together.',
        answer: """Dejectedly 

"""),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question:
            'Her ____ began to fade when she returned to the Sorbonne to succeed her husband.',
        answer: """wretchedness 
"""),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question:
            'Even though she became fatally ill from working with radium, Marie Curie was never ____.',
        answer: """disappointed
"""),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: 'Herculaneum and its harbor were buried under _____ lava.',
        answer: """solid
"""),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: 'The poisonous gases were not ______ in the air.',
        answer: """ able to float 

"""),
  ];

  static List<QuestionAnswer> readingCompreh = [
    QuestionAnswer(
        question:
            """ This is the first section of your IELTS Reading test. You spend about twenty \n
Minutes on it. Read the passage and answer questions 1-13.\n
Making time for science
""",
        answer: """
Chronobiology might sound a little futuristic-like something from a science fiction novel,
Perhaps-but it’s actually a field of study that concerns one of the oldest processes life on this
Planet has ever known: short term rhythms of time and their effect on flora and fauna


This can take many forms. Marine life, for example, is influenced by tidal patterns. Animals tend
To be active or inactive depending on the position of the sun or moon. Numerous creatures,
Humans included, are largely diurnal-that is, they like to come out during the hours of sunlight.
Nocturnal animals, such as bats and possums, prefer to forage by night. A third group is
Known as crepuscular: they thrive in the low-light of dawn and dusk and remain inactive at other
Hours.
When it comes to humans, Chronobiologists are interested in what is known as the circadian
Rhythm. This is the complete cycle our bodies are naturally geared to undergo within the
Passage of a twenty-four hour day.  Aside from sleeping at night and walking during the day. Each 
Not everyone has an identical circadian rhythm ‘Night people’ for example often describe, how
They find it very hard to operate during the morning, but become alert and focused by evening. 
This is a benign variation within circadian rhythms known as cerotype

Knowledge of chronobiological patterns can have many pragmatic implications for our day-to
Day lives while contemporary living can sometimes appear to subjugate biology-after all, who needs circadian rhythms when we have caffeine pills, energy drinks, shift work and cities that
 Never sleep? - Keeping in sync with our body clock is important 

"""),
  ];
}

// ---------------------------------------------------------

class QuestionAnswer {
  final String question;
  final String answer;

  QuestionAnswer({
    required this.question,
    required this.answer,
  });
}
